Mohammed Barsat Zulkarnine

Melbourne VIC 3000 mohammedbarsatzulkarnine@gmail.com +61 475 128 013

Hardworking College Student trying to gain as much experience as I can. Bringing forth a motivated attitude and a variety of powerful skills. Adept in various social media platforms and office technology programs. Committed to utilizing my skills to further the mission of a company. Excellent time management skills combined with superior knowledge of the customer service industry. Bilingual, hardworking, and ready to join my next team.

Personal Details

Eligible to work in Australia: Yes

Highest Level of Education: Secondary School (Year 12)

Total years of experience: 1

Work Experience

Telemarketer/Surveyor

Reduce Your Loans - Gardenvale VIC July 2022 to Present

Calling Victorians and persuading them to complete a survey over the phone. Currently one of the top performers in the survey team since my first week at this place.

Sales Representative

Storm Group Australia - Melbourne VIC June 2022 to July 2022

Working as a sales representative for the Australian Red Cross.

Home Tutor

BDTUTORS - Dhaka August 2021 to February 2022

Provided helpful teaching supports to students who were struggling with online education due to COVID 19. Worked with students in Year 1 to Year 10 to strengthen and support their overall understanding

Education

Bachelor Degree (Hons) in Software Engineering

Swinburne University of Technology - Hawthorn VIC

February 2022 to Present

High School (Year 12)

Skills

- Sales
- Telemarketing
- Microsoft Office
- HTML5
- CSS3